CV for Sumaya Gure

Name: Sumaya Gure

Address: 102 Herrick Road, B8 1PG Birmingham

Mobil: **07878297833 Birth date:** 09.04.1994

Email: sumayabile8@gmail.com

Marital status: Engaged



Key qualifications:

With a bachelor's degree, specializing in maritime logistics, my studies included logistics and management both analysis and numeric studies. Some of the subjects included in my degree courses were economics, macroeconomics, mathematics, supply chain, logistics operation, transportation intelligence, and my thesis research was about the Competitiveness of Logistics Service Providers in China.

A balanced, highly capable, and technically minded young graduate who works well both on their own initiative and in small teams and groups.

I see myself as a social and outgoing person who is motivated to do an excellent job. Like to challenge me in order to grow positively in all aspects of life. Strong communication and customer service skills, meticulous attention to detail, and a person who follows through.

Working experience:

2021- Amazon, Coventry United Kingdom

FC Associate

Fulfillment associates fulfill basic warehousing and stock order duties. I am responsible for unloading merchandise trucks, deciphering work orders, locating stock, and packing items for shipment. Tasks may include Efficiently and effectively receiving & storing goods inwards following Amazon's internal processes and procedures and using radio frequency (RF) scanners

2020-2021 Novo Entreprenør AS, Oslo, Norway

Logistics trainee

During my 8-month trainee period at the construction company Novo, I have worked with logistics.

My team consisted of the general manager and his assistant. I was in charge of the warehouse by checking the security products and the safe clothes for employees and sending feedback to the general manager. I was also

involved in the contact with the seller. The tasks also consisted of going to the project site in Moss to check equipment, including building materials and machinery. In addition, I managed the employment contracts and the archives called and arranged meetings with other companies and agreements for car service for the workers. In the end, I was included in helping the leaders with finances.

2018- 2019 Jabavu village LTD, Nairobi, Kenya

PA for Head Manager

Tasks related to daily management, scheduling of meetings, correspondence with clients, suppliers, and note-taking. Arranging meetings with both domestic and international clients by phone and email. Also responsible for office administration, managing the office with everything such as sending goods with drivers, managing 15 employees, and handling the office budget related to the daily and monthly requirements in the office.

2018 Tøyen Unlimited, Oslo

Administration Accountant

Internal operational accounting duties like payroll, taxes, and management. During the two months of work, I worked with the manager as administrator and accountant and assisted in organizing events.

2017-2018 Workforce staffing LTD, Redditch, UK

Warehouse staff – summer help

Worked as part of a large team of 20 people within the main SP disruption center to oversee the assembly and placement of stock items following the receipt of stock deliveries, including reporting to the warehouse manager. Also did the packing for deliveries to different stations within the UK. For two summers, I gained practical insight into the delivery process connected to my university studies.

2015 Gorcen import-export, Ningbo, China Manager Assistant

Assistant for the head manager in a company that sold safety products. Helped my colleagues in their projects with translations from English to Arabic and contacting international clients with different countries through emails.

Education:

2021-2022 University Of Birmingham-Full stack Development Birmingham-United kingdom

2013–2017 Ningbo University, Maritime faculty – Logistics Management. Ningbo-China

2010–2012 Al-Bahrain High school, General Subjects Hargeisa-Somalia

2007-2010. Al-Siyahiya school, Middle school Damascus-Syria

2000-2008 Al Qashom primary school/ Horna school Damascus-Syria

Further education:

2010 Computer programs.

2012-2013 Two years in Medicine faculty

2017 Rosenhof Norwegian course [10 weeks]
2019 Din Utvikling English job course [4 weeks]
2019 Podium arbeid og kommunikasjon [16 weeks]

2020 Supply chain management course in University of New Jersey [4 weeks]

2021 Accounting course [50 Hours]

Certificates: First Aid, OIW Nordic China tech summit, member of toastmasters, Accounting, supply chain management.

Data/computer skills: -Microsoft Office

- Social Media Proficient

- Outlook

Other:

2021- Business partner in Opulence Global

Canada

Established in 2005, Opulence Global is home to Canada's largest designer fashion house and other major product sectors, including skincare, personal care, and health & wellness, dedicated to design and manufacturing products that impact your life. Our mission is to provide you with an optimum lifestyle, optimum beauty, and optimum health.

2020- Church's city and red cross non-Profit organization. Oslo. Norway

I work as an environmental coordinator worker and a translator between Norwegian English Somali and Arabic health centers. The health center is run by the Red Cross and the Church's city mission and offers free interdisciplinary health care for persons without a valid residence permit in Norway.

2020- Church's city non-profit organization volunteering center summer activities

I work there as a volunteer to assist my community with the summer activities for the kids and families. During the holidays we provide a nice event or a good trip.

2019-2021 Corporation's manager	and a productive member of NCEF -Norway
---------------------------------	---

2018-	Vice president of Hooyo power organization in -Norway
2015-2017	Volunteered at blood donations organizationsChina
2015-2017	Vice president for international toastmaster's club -China
2013-2017	Member of the student union in Ningbo University -China

2014-2016 Volunteered at schools, teaching Chinese kids English and Arabic language. -China

Languages:

Norwegian Advanced orally and written.
English Fluent orally and written.
Arabic Fluent both orally and written.
Turkish Advanced orally and written.

Somali Native speaker

Mandarin Good orally, basic writing.

Korean level A1 (learning)

Interests: Cycling, puzzles, reading & research, swimming, Numismatics, and walking

References: Given upon requests.